{
    "subject": "resource/Body_of_Evidence_(1993_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/producer",
    "object": "resource/Dino_De_Laurentiis",
    "human_readable": "The producer of the film Body of Evidence is Dino De Laurentiis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9753397107124329,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Dino De Laurentiis."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9673618674278259,
            "question": "Is Dino De Laurentiis a known film producer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9595358967781067,
            "question": "What film did Dino De Laurentiis produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9169557094573975,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a movie produced by Dino De Laurentiis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8996462821960449,
            "question": "Dino De Laurentiis is famous for producing which type of films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8718845844268799,
            "question": "What other films might Dino De Laurentiis have produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8419238924980164,
            "question": "Who produced the film Body of Evidence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.72613924741745,
            "question": "What is the name of the producer of Body of Evidence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6163501143455505,
            "question": "Who directed the film Body of Evidence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22653540968894958,
            "question": "What year was Body of Evidence released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The producer of the film Body of Evidence is Dino De Laurentiis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_202_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed the film Body of Evidence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_202_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the producer of Body of Evidence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_202_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who produced the film Body of Evidence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_202_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_202_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_202_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_202_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_202_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_202_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_202_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_202_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_202_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_202_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_202_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. In several documents, Dino De Laurentiis is mentioned as the producer or co-producer of various films, including \"Body of Evidence\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Dino De Laurentiis was involved with the production of the film \"Body of Evidence,\" as it mentions \"MGM and Dino De Laurentiis' 'Body of Evidence'\" in multiple contexts."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}